<dashboard version="1.1" script="securityjourney.js" stylesheet="securityjourney.css">
  <!-- Updated Label for Data Compliance Pipelines -->
  <label>Data Compliance Maturity</label>
  <row>
    <panel>
      <html>
        <!-- Note: Layout is controlled by the updated securityjourney.css with media queries for
        desktop and widescreen monitors -->
        <div class="clearfix">
          <div class="column">
            <!-- Side Panel Content Area (First Column) -->
            <div class="stageinfo" id="stagedesc">
              <span class="stageinfoheader">
                DESCRIPTION
              </span>
              <br />
              <span class="stageinfocontent" id="stagedesccontent">
                <!-- Content will be dynamically loaded here by JS -->
              </span>
            </div>
            <div class="stageinfo" id="stagemilestones">
              <span class="stageinfoheader">
                MILESTONES
              </span>
              <br />
              <span class="stageinfocontent" id="stagemilestonecontent">
                <!-- Content will be dynamically loaded here by JS -->
              </span>
            </div>
            <div class="stageinfo" id="stagechallenges">
              <span class="stageinfoheader">
                CHALLENGES
              </span>
              <br />
              <span class="stageinfocontent" id="stagechallengecontent">
                <!-- Content will be dynamically loaded here by JS -->
              </span>
            </div>
          </div>
          <div class="column stagetablediv">
            <!-- Maturity Steps Table (Second Column) -->
            <table id="stagetable">
              <tr>
                <td class="slidercell" rowspan="7">
                  <input id="journeyslider" class="journey-slider" type="range" min="0" max="1000" />
                </td>
                <td>
                  <div class="topstagename">STEP 6
                  </div>
                </td>
              </tr>
              <tr>
                <td>
                  <!-- Step 6 -->
                  <div id="stage6" class="roundcorners stageheight stage stage6 stage6dark">
                    <div class="journeystagename"> Automate &amp; Optimize <!-- Updated -->
                    </div>
                    <div class="journeystagedesc"> Automate compliance tasks, integrate workflows,
                      and continuously improve posture. <!-- Updated -->
                    </div>
                  </div>
                  <div class="stageheight stagename">
                    STEP 5
                  </div>
                </td>
              </tr>
              <tr>
                <td>
                  <!-- Step 5 -->
                  <div id="stage5" class="roundcorners stageheight stage stage5 stage5dark">
                    <div class="journeystagename"> Audit &amp; Report Evidence <!-- Updated -->
                    </div>
                    <div class="journeystagedesc"> Streamline evidence gathering and generate
                      compliance reports for auditors/stakeholders. <!-- Updated -->
                    </div>
                  </div>
                  <div class="stageheight stagename">
                    STEP 4
                  </div>
                </td>
              </tr>
              <tr>
                <td>
                  <!-- Step 4 -->
                  <div id="stage4" class="roundcorners stageheight stage stage4 stage4dark">
                    <div class="journeystagename"> Monitor &amp; Detect Deviations <!-- Updated -->
                    </div>
                    <div class="journeystagedesc"> Continuously monitor control effectiveness and
                      detect policy violations or anomalies. <!-- Updated -->
                    </div>
                  </div>
                  <div class="stageheight stagename">
                    STEP 3
                  </div>
                </td>
              </tr>
              <tr>
                <td>
                  <!-- Step 3 -->
                  <div id="stage3" class="roundcorners stageheight stage stage3 stage3dark">
                    <div class="journeystagename"> Implement &amp; Enforce <!-- Updated -->
                    </div>
                    <div class="journeystagedesc"> Deploy technical controls (access, encryption,
                      logging) and procedural safeguards. <!-- Updated -->
                    </div>
                  </div>
                  <div class="stageheight stagename">
                    STEP 2
                  </div>
                </td>
              </tr>
              <tr>
                <td>
                  <!-- Step 2 -->
                  <div id="stage2" class="roundcorners stageheight stage stage2 stage2dark">
                    <div class="journeystagename"> Define Policies &amp; Controls <!-- Updated -->
                    </div>
                    <div class="journeystagedesc"> Establish clear data handling policies and map
                      required security/privacy controls. <!-- Updated -->
                    </div>
                  </div>
                  <div class="stageheight stagename">
                    STEP 1
                  </div>
                </td>
              </tr>
              <tr>
                <td>
                  <!-- Step 1 -->
                  <div id="stage1" class="roundcorners stageheight stage stage1">
                    <div class="journeystagename"> Discover &amp; Classify <!-- Updated -->
                    </div>
                    <div class="journeystagedesc"> Identify applicable regulations (PCI, <a href="https://gdpr-info.eu/">GDPR</a>, FSI,
                      etc.) and locate/classify sensitive data. <!-- Updated -->
                    </div>
                  </div>
                </td>
              </tr>
            </table>
          </div>
          <div class="column">
            <!-- Selected Step Indicator (Third Column) -->
            <div id="selectedstage" class="selectedstage">
              <span>SELECTED STEP</span>
            </div>
            <div id="numbercircle" class="numberCircle">1 <!-- Default to 1, JS updates this -->
            </div>
          </div>
        </div>

        <!-- Hidden divs containing detailed content for each step -->
        <!-- Updated Content for Step 1 -->
        <div id="stage1description" class="dontshow">
          This initial step focuses on understanding the compliance landscape relevant to your
          organization and identifying where sensitive data resides. It involves inventorying data
          assets, classifying data based on sensitivity and regulatory requirements (e.g., PCI CDE,
          PII under <a href="https://gdpr-info.eu/">GDPR</a>, NPI under GLBA), and mapping data flows to understand how sensitive
          information moves through systems.
        </div>
        <div id="stage1milestone" class="dontshow"> Successfully completing this stage means: <ul>
            <li>You have identified the specific regulations (<a href="https://www.pcisecuritystandards.org/">PCI DSS</a>, <a href="https://gdpr-info.eu/">GDPR</a>, <a href="https://oag.ca.gov/privacy/ccpa">CCPA</a>, SOX, FSI
              mandates, etc.) applicable to your business.</li>
            <li>You have created or updated a data inventory that identifies critical and sensitive
          data assets.</li>
            <li>Data classification standards are defined and applied, distinguishing between
              public, internal, confidential, and restricted data.</li>
            <li>You have a basic understanding of where key regulated data resides within your IT
          environment (databases, file shares, applications, cloud storage).</li>
          </ul>
        </div>
        <div id="stage1challenge" class="dontshow"> Challenges at this stage often include: <ul>
            <li>Discovering data hidden in unexpected locations (e.g., unstructured data, shadow
              IT).</li>
            <li>Accurately classifying large volumes of data across diverse systems.</li>
            <li>Keeping the data inventory and classification up-to-date as the environment changes.</li>
            <li>Dealing with complex data flows across on-premises and cloud environments.</li>
          </ul>
        </div>

        <!-- Updated Content for Step 2 -->
        <div id="stage2description" class="dontshow">
          Based on the regulations identified and data classified in Step 1, this stage involves
          defining clear, actionable policies for data handling, security, and privacy. It also
          includes selecting the specific technical and procedural controls required to meet the
          mandates of frameworks like <a href="https://www.pcisecuritystandards.org/">PCI DSS</a>, <a href="https://gdpr-info.eu/">GDPR</a>, etc. This involves translating regulatory
          requirements into concrete control objectives.
        </div>
        <div id="stage2milestone" class="dontshow"> Key milestones for this stage include: <ul>
            <li>Documented policies covering data access, use, storage, retention, disposal, and
          incident response are established or updated.</li>
            <li>Specific security controls (e.g., encryption standards, access control mechanisms,
          logging requirements, vulnerability management) are selected based on risk assessments and
          regulatory requirements (e.g., mapping controls to <a href="https://www.pcisecuritystandards.org/">PCI DSS</a> requirements).</li>
            <li>Privacy controls (e.g., consent mechanisms, data minimization procedures, DSAR
          processes) are defined.</li>
            <li>Control ownership and responsibilities are clearly assigned within the organization.</li>
          </ul>
        </div>
        <div id="stage2challenge" class="dontshow"> Common challenges involve: <ul>
            <li>Translating high-level regulatory text into specific, implementable controls.</li>
            <li>Balancing security/compliance requirements with business operational needs.</li>
            <li>Ensuring policies are clearly communicated and understood across the organization.</li>
            <li>Selecting appropriate controls that are both effective and feasible to implement and
          manage.</li>
          </ul>
        </div>

        <!-- Updated Content for Step 3 -->
        <div id="stage3description" class="dontshow">
          This stage focuses on the practical deployment and enforcement of the policies and
          controls defined in Step 2. It involves configuring security tools, implementing technical
          safeguards (like encryption and access controls), establishing required logging, and
          putting procedural mechanisms into practice across the relevant systems and processes
          handling sensitive data.
        </div>
        <div id="stage3milestone" class="dontshow"> Achieving this stage means: <ul>
            <li>Required technical security controls (firewalls, IDS/IPS, endpoint security,
          encryption for data-at-rest/in-transit) are deployed and configured according to policy.</li>
            <li>Access control mechanisms (e.g., RBAC, MFA) are implemented to enforce least
          privilege principles for sensitive data.</li>
            <li>Comprehensive logging is enabled on critical systems as required by regulations
          (e.g., <a href="https://www.pcisecuritystandards.org/">PCI DSS</a> Req 10) and logs are centrally collected.</li>
            <li>Procedural controls (e.g., change management processes, employee training on data
          handling) are actively enforced.</li>
            <li>Data Loss Prevention (DLP) solutions may be implemented to monitor and block
          unauthorized data exfiltration.</li>
          </ul>
        </div>
        <div id="stage3challenge" class="dontshow"> Implementation challenges often include: <ul>
            <li>Integrating new security tools with existing infrastructure.</li>
            <li>Ensuring consistent control implementation across diverse environments (on-prem,
          cloud, legacy systems).</li>
            <li>Minimizing disruption to business operations during control deployment.</li>
            <li>Achieving adequate log coverage and ensuring logs are protected and forwarded
          reliably.</li>
            <li>Overcoming user resistance to new security procedures or controls.</li>
          </ul>
        </div>

        <!-- Updated Content for Step 4 -->
        <div id="stage4description" class="dontshow">
          With controls implemented, this stage focuses on continuous monitoring to ensure they are
          operating effectively and detecting deviations from policies or potential compliance
          violations. It involves actively analyzing logs and events, running vulnerability scans,
          performing configuration checks, and using security analytics to identify anomalies
          indicative of risks or non-compliance.
        </div>
        <div id="stage4milestone" class="dontshow"> Key milestones include: <ul>
            <li>Security Information and Event Management (SIEM) or a platform like Splunk is used
              to correlate and analyze logs for security and compliance events.</li>
            <li>Automated alerts are configured to notify personnel of critical security events,
          policy violations, or control failures (e.g., unauthorized access attempts, critical file
          modifications).</li>
            <li>Regular vulnerability scanning and penetration testing are performed to identify
          weaknesses.</li>
            <li>Configuration management tools monitor systems for unauthorized changes or
              deviations from secure baselines.</li>
            <li>User activity monitoring is in place for privileged accounts and access to sensitive
          data.</li>
          </ul>
        </div>
        <div id="stage4challenge" class="dontshow"> Monitoring challenges typically involve: <ul>
            <li>Dealing with a high volume of logs and alerts (alert fatigue).</li>
            <li>Tuning detection rules to minimize false positives while catching true threats.</li>
            <li>Correlating events across different data sources to get a complete picture.</li>
            <li>Monitoring encrypted traffic and activities within cloud environments.</li>
            <li>Ensuring monitoring processes cover all relevant systems and data subject to
          compliance.</li>
          </ul>
        </div>

        <!-- Updated Content for Step 5 -->
        <div id="stage5description" class="dontshow">
          This stage focuses on efficiently gathering evidence of control effectiveness and
          generating the necessary reports for internal stakeholders, management, and external
          auditors (e.g., PCI QSA, FSI regulators, privacy authorities). It involves streamlining
          the process of demonstrating compliance through organized data, dashboards, and formalized
          reporting.
        </div>
        <div id="stage5milestone" class="dontshow"> Successfully reaching this stage means: <ul>
            <li>Compliance dashboards provide real-time visibility into key control metrics and
          compliance posture.</li>
            <li>Processes are established to quickly retrieve specific logs and evidence required by
          auditors (e.g., demonstrating access controls for PCI Req 7, audit trails for PCI Req 10).</li>
            <li>Automated or semi-automated reports mapped to specific regulatory requirements
              (e.g., PCI Attestation of Compliance support, <a href="https://gdpr-info.eu/">GDPR</a> Article 30 records) can be
          generated.</li>
            <li>Audit findings are tracked, and remediation efforts are documented.</li>
            <li>Clear documentation exists detailing how controls meet specific regulatory
          requirements.</li>
          </ul>
        </div>
        <div id="stage5challenge" class="dontshow"> Challenges in auditing and reporting include: <ul>
            <li>Manually gathering evidence from disparate systems is time-consuming and
              error-prone.</li>
            <li>Mapping technical evidence to specific, often non-technical, compliance
              requirements.</li>
            <li>Ensuring the integrity and completeness of audit evidence.</li>
            <li>Generating reports in the specific formats required by different auditors or
          regulations.</li>
            <li>Keeping documentation current with environmental and regulatory changes.</li>
          </ul>
        </div>

        <!-- Updated Content for Step 6 -->
        <div id="stage6description" class="dontshow">
          This represents the highest level of data compliance maturity. Activities focus on
          automating compliance processes, integrating security and privacy workflows, and
          leveraging data analytics for continuous improvement and proactive risk reduction. It
          involves moving beyond reactive reporting to predictive insights and automated remediation
          where possible. Compliance is deeply embedded into operations (Compliance-as-Code
          principles may apply).
        </div>
        <div id="stage6milestone" class="dontshow"> At this step, your organization has achieved a
          state of continuous compliance readiness: <ul>
            <li>Key compliance monitoring, evidence gathering, and reporting tasks are largely
          automated, reducing manual effort and errors.</li>
            <li>Data from security, IT operations, and privacy tools are integrated, providing
          holistic visibility and context (e.g., correlating security alerts with potential privacy
          impacts).</li>
            <li>Workflows for tasks like Data Subject Access Requests (DSARs), breach response, and
          control testing are automated and orchestrated.</li>
            <li>Advanced analytics and potentially Machine Learning are used to identify subtle
          compliance risks, predict potential issues, and optimize control effectiveness.</li>
            <li>Compliance metrics are actively tracked, reported, and used to drive strategic
          decisions regarding risk management and resource allocation.</li>
            <li>Regular reviews and optimizations ensure controls remain effective against evolving
          threats and regulations.</li>
          </ul>
        </div>
        <div id="stage6challenge" class="dontshow"> Maintaining this level requires ongoing
          commitment and adaptation: <ul>
            <li>Keeping automation scripts and integrations up-to-date with changing regulations and
          evolving IT environments is a constant task.</li>
            <li>Ensuring the accuracy and reliability of automated reporting and alerting requires
          robust validation and testing.</li>
            <li>Integrating diverse toolsets and data sources across security, privacy, and IT can
          present technical and organizational hurdles.</li>
            <li>Developing and maintaining the in-house expertise (or leveraging partners) for
          advanced analytics and automation requires investment.</li>
            <li>Avoiding "automation complacency" - ensuring that automated processes are still
          regularly reviewed and validated by human experts.</li>
          </ul>
        </div>
      </html>
    </panel>
  </row>
</dashboard>