<dashboard version="1.1" theme="light" script="tabs.js" stylesheet="tabs.css">
   <!-- Updated Label -->
   <label>Introduction to Data Compliance Pipelines</label>
   <!-- Updated Description -->
   <description>Understanding Key Data Compliance Regulations and Governed Data Types</description>
   <row>
      <panel>
         <html>
            <h1>
               <!-- Placeholder: Update icon path -->
               <img width="40"
                  src="/static/app/Data_Compliance_Pipelines/SA_image_icon_target.png" />
               <b>INTRODUCTION</b>
            </h1>
            <ul>
               <!-- Updated Introduction Text -->
               <p>Meeting today's complex web of data compliance pipelines and mandates—spanning
                  security-focused frameworks like <a href="https://www.pcisecuritystandards.org/">PCI
                  DSS</a>, operational regulations like SOX, and privacy-centric laws such as <a
                     href="https://gdpr-info.eu/">GDPR</a> and <a
                     href="https://oag.ca.gov/privacy/ccpa">CCPA</a>, alongside numerous
                  FSI-specific requirements—is a non-negotiable aspect of modern business. It's
                  crucial to understand the interplay between <strong>Data Security</strong>
                  (protecting data from unauthorized access, corruption, or theft through technical
                  controls) and <strong>Data Privacy</strong> (governing how personal data is
                  collected, used, stored, shared, and ensuring individual rights). While distinct,
                  they are deeply intertwined: robust data security is the essential foundation upon
                  which data privacy compliance is built, and data compliance pipelines are the
                  mechanism for achieving this at scale.</p>
               <p>Organizations face significant hurdles in achieving compliance across both
                  domains. Fragmented data silos and disconnected data compliance pipelines across
                  hybrid and multi-cloud environments obscure visibility, evolving regulations
                  demand constant adaptation, and reliance on manual checks and periodic audits
                  creates gaps and inefficiencies. Splunk provides a unified data platform capable
                  of ingesting, normalizing, and analyzing machine data from any source. This unique
                  ability to break down data silos and unify compliance pipelines allows
                  organizations to continuously monitor security controls, gather evidence for
                  privacy adherence, streamline auditing, and accelerate incident response,
                  providing the foundational visibility required to manage the complexities of both
                  data security and data privacy regulations.</p>
            </ul>
         </html>
      </panel>
   </row>
   <row id="tabs">
      <panel>
         <html>
            <p>
               <ul id="tabs" class="nav nav-tabs">
                  <li>
                     <!-- Placeholder: Update nav button image -->
                     <img width="200"
                        src="/static/app/Data_Compliance_Pipelines/SA_image_icon_navi_gr_button.png" />
                  </li>
                  <li class="active">
                     <a href="#" class="toggle-tab" data-toggle="tab" data-elements="tab_objective">1
                        | OBJECTIVE</a>
                  </li>
                  <li>
                     <a href="#" class="toggle-tab" data-toggle="tab" data-elements="tab_data_types">2
                        |
                        DATA TYPES</a>
                  </li>
                  <li>
                     <!-- Placeholder: Update Lantern link for Compliance -->
                     <a
                        href="https://lantern.splunk.com/Security/UCE/Foundational_Visibility/Compliance"
                        target="_blank">3 | LANTERN RECIPES</a>
                  </li>
                  <li>
                     <a href="#" class="toggle-tab" data-toggle="tab" data-elements="tab_help">4 |
                        HELP</a>
                  </li>
               </ul>
            </p>
         </html>
      </panel>
   </row>
   <row id="tab_objective">
      <panel>
         <html>
            <ul>
               <h1>
                  <!-- Placeholder: Update icon path -->
                  <img width="35"
                     src="/static/app/Data_Compliance_Pipelines/SA_image_icon_target.png" />
                  <b>OBJECTIVE:</b>
               </h1>
               <!-- Updated Objective Text -->
               <p>The primary objective of data compliance initiatives is to ensure adherence to
                  relevant laws, regulations, industry standards, and internal policies governing
                  data security and privacy. This involves implementing and maintaining appropriate
                  technical and organizational controls to protect sensitive information (like
                  customer PII, financial data, cardholder data) and demonstrating this adherence to
                  auditors and regulators.</p>
               <p>Key goals often include: <ul>
                     <ul>
                        <li>
                           <b>Meeting Regulatory Requirements:</b> Satisfying specific mandates from
                  frameworks like <a href="https://www.pcisecuritystandards.org/">PCI DSS</a> (e.g.,
                  Requirement 10 for logging, Requirement 7 for access control), <a
                              href="https://gdpr-info.eu/">GDPR</a> (e.g., data subject rights,
                  breach notification), SOX (financial reporting controls), and various FSI
                  regulations.</li>
                        <li>
                           <b>Protecting Sensitive Data:</b> Implementing robust security controls
                  (encryption, access management, vulnerability management) to prevent data breaches
                  and unauthorized access.</li>
                        <li>
                           <b>Ensuring Data Privacy:</b> Managing data according to privacy
                  principles, including consent management, purpose limitation, data minimization,
                  and honoring data subject rights (like DSARs).</li>
                        <li>
                           <b>Streamlining Audits:</b> Reducing the effort and cost associated with
                  compliance audits by centralizing evidence, automating control monitoring, and
                  simplifying reporting.</li>
                        <li>
                           <b>Managing Risk:</b> Proactively identifying and mitigating compliance
                  risks related to data handling, security posture, and third-party vendors.</li>
                        <li>
                           <b>Building Trust:</b> Demonstrating a commitment to data protection,
                  thereby enhancing customer confidence and brand reputation.</li>
                     </ul>
                  </ul>
               </p>
               <p>An effective data compliance program leverages continuous monitoring and data
                  analysis to provide assurance that controls are working as intended and that the
                  organization can quickly respond to potential issues, minimizing financial, legal,
                  and reputational damage.</p>
            </ul>
            <hr width="100%" />
            <ul>
               <h1>
                  <!-- Placeholder: Update icon path -->
                  <img width="35"
                     src="/static/app/Data_Compliance_Pipelines/SA_image_icon_target.png" />
                  <b>PREREQUISITES:</b>
               </h1>
               <!-- Updated Prerequisites Text -->
               <p>To effectively navigate the complex, fragmented, and regionally diverse data
                  compliance landscape, gaining comprehensive visibility and enabling the crucial
                  interplay between assets and identities requires the ingestion and analysis of
                  specific data types from across your IT environment. These data sources serve as
                  the foundational inputs for monitoring controls, detecting deviations, and
                  providing the necessary audit trails across various regulatory mandates.</p>
               <p>The following data types are typically required for comprehensive data compliance
                  pipeline monitoring and auditing within this Solution Accelerator:</p>
               <ul>
                  <ul>
                     <li>
                        <b>Authentication &amp; Access Logs:</b> Essential for monitoring identity
                        activity and access to assets. System, application, database, and VPN logs
                        showing user logins (success/failure), access attempts to sensitive
                        resources, and privilege escalations are critical. (e.g., Windows Security
                        Events, Linux auth logs, Active Directory logs, Cloud IAM logs).</li>
                     <li>
                        <b>Change Management Logs:</b> Key for tracking modifications to critical
                        assets and configurations that could impact security posture and compliance.
                        Records of changes to system configurations, firewall rules, user
                        permissions, and application code are necessary. (e.g., Config management
                        tool logs, Git logs, OS change logs).</li>
                     <li>
                        <b>Network Activity Logs:</b> Provide visibility into the flow of data (a
                        key asset) and potential policy violations across the network. Firewall,
                        proxy, IDS/IPS, and network flow data showing traffic patterns, connection
                        attempts, and potential policy violations are valuable.</li>
                     <li>
                        <b>Endpoint Security Logs:</b> Offer insights into the security status of
                        endpoints (assets) and potential threats impacting data.
                        Antivirus/anti-malware alerts, host-based intrusion detection events, file
                        integrity monitoring alerts, and DLP events are important for compliance
                        monitoring.</li>
                     <li>
                        <b>Operating System Logs:</b> Provide granular audit trails at the OS level
                        (an asset), capturing system events, process execution, and critical errors
                        relevant to compliance. (e.g., Windows Event Logs, Linux syslog).</li>
                     <li>
                        <b>Database Audit Logs:</b> Crucial for monitoring access to sensitive data
                        (an asset) within databases and tracking administrative actions and schema
                        changes. Logs tracking access to sensitive tables/data, administrative
                        actions, and changes to database schemas or permissions are vital.</li>
                     <li>
                        <b>Cloud Infrastructure Logs:</b> Provide audit trails for cloud assets and
                        identities, detailing API calls, resource modifications, security group
                        changes, and access events within cloud environments. (e.g., AWS CloudTrail,
                        Azure Activity Log, GCP Audit Logs).</li>
                     <li>
                        <b>Vulnerability Scan Data</b> (Optional): Results from vulnerability
                        scanners identifying weaknesses in systems (assets) that could lead to
                        non-compliance.</li>
                     <li>
                        <b>Asset &amp; Identity Data</b> (Optional): Explicit information
                        correlating systems/IPs to owners/functions (assets) and users to
                        roles/permissions (identities). While inferred from other logs, explicit
                        data enhances correlation and analysis.</li>
                  </ul>
               </ul>
               <br />
               <p>Centralizing and correlating these diverse data inputs is fundamental to the
                  Solution Accelerator for Data Compliance Pipelines's ability to provide the
                  necessary visibility for compliance across various regulations and to effectively
                  monitor the interactions between assets and identities through unified data
                  compliance pipelines.</p>
            </ul>
         </html>
      </panel>
   </row>
   <row id="tab_data_types">
      <panel>
         <html>
            <ul>
               <h1>
                  <!-- Placeholder: Update icon path -->
                  <img width="35"
                     src="/static/app/Data_Compliance_Pipelines/SA_image_icon_target.png" />
                  <b>KEY DATA CATEGORIES: Information Governed by Compliance Regulations</b>
               </h1>
               <!-- Expanded Data Types Text -->
               <p>Data compliance regulations are primarily focused on protecting specific
                  categories of sensitive and regulated information. Understanding where these data
                  types exist within your environment is fundamental to identifying your compliance
                  obligations and implementing appropriate technical and organizational controls as
                  mandated by various global and regional frameworks.</p>
               <ul>
                  <li>
                     <b>Personally Identifiable Information (PII):</b> This is information that can
                     directly or indirectly identify an individual. Its definition can vary slightly
                     by jurisdiction, but generally includes details like names, addresses, email
                     addresses, phone numbers, identification numbers (such as social security or
                     national ID), and sometimes even online identifiers or location data. PII is a
                     core focus of comprehensive privacy regulations worldwide, such as the <a
                        href="https://gdpr-info.eu/">GDPR</a> in Europe, <a
                        href="https://oag.ca.gov/privacy/ccpa">CCPA</a>/<a
                        href="https://thecpra.org/">CPRA</a> in the United States, LGPD in Brazil,
                     and numerous national data protection acts across APJC and other regions.
                     Compliance requires careful handling based on principles like consent, purpose
                     limitation, data minimization, and ensuring data subject rights. </li>
                  <li>
                     <b>Financial Data:</b> This encompasses information related to an individual's
                     or entity's financial standing, transactions, accounts, investments, and credit
                     history. Due to its sensitive nature and direct link to economic activity,
                     financial data is subject to rigorous regulations globally. These include
                     sector-specific laws (like GLBA in the US), anti-money laundering (AML) and
                     counter-terrorist financing (CFT) mandates (ubiquitous worldwide), and
                     requirements from financial regulatory bodies in each region (e.g., MAS in
                     Singapore, BaFin in Germany, FCA/PRA in the UK). Compliance focuses on data
                     security, transaction monitoring, record-keeping, and reporting obligations. </li>
                  <li>
                     <b>Cardholder Data (CHD):</b> This specific set of data elements is required
                     for processing payment card transactions and is the central focus of the
                     Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (<a
                        href="https://www.pcisecuritystandards.org/">PCI DSS</a>). CHD includes the
                     Primary Account Number (PAN), cardholder name, expiration date, and service
                     code. While <a href="https://www.pcisecuritystandards.org/">PCI DSS</a> is a
                     global standard mandated by card brands, the handling of CHD is often also
                     subject to national data privacy and security laws, requiring adherence to both <a
                        href="https://www.pcisecuritystandards.org/">PCI DSS</a> and relevant local
                     regulations. </li>
                  <li>
                     <b>Protected Health Information (PHI):</b> This refers to information related
                     to an individual's past, present, or future physical or mental health, the
                     provision of healthcare, or payment for healthcare. While HIPAA is a prominent
                     example in the United States, many countries have specific health data privacy
                     laws or include health data as a "special category" of sensitive personal data
                     under general privacy laws (as in <a href="https://gdpr-info.eu/">GDPR</a>).
                     Handling PHI requires strict access controls, security measures, and adherence
                     to consent and usage restrictions tailored to health sector regulations. </li>
                  <li>
                     <b>Proprietary and Confidential Business Data:</b> Beyond individual privacy,
                     regulations often mandate the protection of sensitive business information
                     crucial for operational integrity, financial reporting, and market stability.
                     This can include internal financial records, trade secrets, intellectual
                     property, strategic plans, and data critical to operational resilience.
                     Frameworks like SOX (focusing on financial reporting data controls), DORA
                     (emphasizing IT security and resilience for financial entities), and APRA's CPS
                     standards (covering information security and operational resilience in
                     Australia) often require controls around these data types to ensure business
                     continuity and prevent systemic risk. </li>
               </ul>
               <br />
               <p>Effectively managing data compliance across this diverse landscape requires
                  identifying where these various types of regulated data reside within your hybrid
                  and multi-cloud environments and applying the necessary security, privacy, and
                  operational controls as dictated by the specific regulations applicable to your
                  organization's operations and the jurisdictions in which you operate.</p>
            </ul>
         </html>
      </panel>
   </row>
   <row id="tab_help">
      <panel>
         <html tokens="true">
            <ul>
               <h1>
                  <!-- Placeholder: Update icon path -->
                  <img width="45"
                     src="/static/app/Data_Compliance_Pipelines/SA_image_icon_ques.png" />
                  <!-- Updated Help Header -->
                  <b>HELP: Ask a Data Compliance Expert</b>
               </h1>
               <p> Need help with your environment or requirements? Send us your questions, and
                  we’ll get back to you as soon as possible. <ul>
                     <li> For detailed step-by-step instructions on implementing the solution using
                  this Solutions Accelerator, visit our <a
                           href="https://lantern.splunk.com/Industry_Use_Cases/Financial_Services_and_Insurance/Solution_Accelerator_for_Data_Compliance_Pipelines">
                           <b>Solutions Accelerator</b>
                        </a> page.</li>
                     <li> To expedite implementation with professional services, please reach out to
                  our sales team by clicking <a
                           href="https://www.splunk.com/en_us/ask-an-expert.html?expertCode=data_compliance_solutions_accelerator"
                           target="_ask_expert">
                           <b>Contact Us</b>
                        </a>
                     </li>
                     <li> If you need immediate assistance, explore our community forum, <a
                           href="http://answers.splunk.com/">
                           <b>Splunk Answers</b>
                        </a>.</li>
                  </ul>
               </p>
               <!-- Placeholder: Update bullet image path -->
               <img src="/static/app/Data_Compliance_Pipelines/SA_image_bullet_03.png" />
               <a
                  href="https://www.splunk.com/en_us/ask-an-expert.html?expertCode=data_compliance_solutions_accelerator"
                  class="btn" target="_ask_expert">Contact Us</a>
            </ul>
         </html>
      </panel>
   </row>

</dashboard> 