<!-- 
    Dashboard Refactored for: Solution Accelerator for Data Compliance Pipelines
  Focus: General Data Compliance, PCI DSS, FSI Regulations
  Original Structure: Retained (Tabs, JS/CSS)
  Content: Completely rewritten for compliance focus.
  Placeholders: Update image paths, Lantern links, and expert codes.
-->
<dashboard version="1.1" theme="light" script="tabs.js" stylesheet="tabs.css">
    <label>Introduction</label>
    <row>
        <panel>
            <html>
                <img height="500" usemap="#nav_banner_map"
                    src="/static/app/Data_Compliance/FSI_Data_Compliance_banner.jpg" />
                <h1>
                    <img width="45" src="/static/app/Data_Compliance/SA_image_icon_07.png" />
                    WELCOME TO SPLUNK SOLUTIONS ACCELERATOR: <font color="#006d9c">Data Compliance
                    Pipelines</font>
                </h1>
                <p> Explore the <b>Solution Accelerator for Data Compliance Pipelines</b> to access
                    solution components designed to jump-start your journey to monitor, audit, and
                    report on compliance pipelines for mandates like <a
                        href="https://www.pcisecuritystandards.org/"
                        target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">PCI DSS</a> and <a
                        href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Financial_services" target="_blank"
                        rel="noopener noreferrer">FSI</a> regulations. This accelerator helps you orchestrate, automate, and gain visibility into your end-to-end data compliance pipelines across hybrid environments.</p>
                <p> Use the <b>navigation tab</b> to understand the challenges of managing compliance pipelines, discover how Splunk enables unified monitoring and automation, and find ready-to-use examples.</p>
            </html>
        </panel>
    </row>
    <row id="tabs">
        <panel>
            <html>
                <ul id="tabs" class="nav nav-tabs">
                    <li>
                        <!-- Placeholder: Update nav button image -->
                        <img width="200"
                            src="/static/app/Data_Compliance/SA_image_icon_navi_gr_button.png" />
                    </li>
                    <li class="active">
                        <a href="#" class="toggle-tab" data-toggle="tab" data-elements="tab_01">
                            1 | INTRODUCTION TO DATA COMPLIANCE PIPELINES
                        </a>
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <a href="#" class="toggle-tab" data-toggle="tab" data-elements="tab_02">
                            2 | WHY SPLUNK FOR DATA COMPLIANCE PIPELINES?
                        </a>
                    </li>
                    <!-- Add more tabs here if needed for specific regulations like PCI, FSI -->
                    <li>
                        <a href="#" class="toggle-tab" data-toggle="tab" data-elements="tab_03">
                            3 | REFERENCE ARCHITECTURE
                        </a>
                    </li>
                </ul>
            </html>
        </panel>
    </row>
    <!-- UPDATE: INTRODUCTION TAB -->
    <row id="tab_01">
        <panel>
            <html>
                <h1>
                    <!-- Placeholder: Update icon -->
                    <img width="45" src="/static/app/Data_Compliance/SA_image_icon_target.png" />
                    <b>INTRODUCTION TO DATA COMPLIANCE PIPELINES CHALLENGES</b>
                </h1>
                <ul>
                    <h2>Navigating the evolving data compliance pipelines landscape
                        for Financial Services</h2>
                    <table>
                        <tr>
                            <td>
                                <h3>The Complex and Evolving Data Compliance Pipelines Landscape</h3>
                                <p>The contemporary financial services sector is contending with a
                                    rapidly shifting and increasingly intricate data compliance pipelines landscape. Today, compliance is no longer a matter of simply ticking boxes—it demands sophisticated, holistic strategies to manage the constant flux of regulatory requirements such as <a
                                        href="https://www.pcisecuritystandards.org/" target="_blank"
                                        rel="noopener noreferrer">PCI DSS</a>, <a
                                        href="https://www.congress.gov/bill/107th-congress/house-bill/3763"
                                        target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">SOX</a>, <a
                                        href="https://gdpr-info.eu/" target="_blank"
                                        rel="noopener noreferrer">GDPR</a>, <a
                                        href="https://oag.ca.gov/privacy/ccpa" target="_blank"
                                        rel="noopener noreferrer">CCPA</a>, and a host of <a
                                        href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Financial_services"
                                        target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">financial industry-specific</a> mandates. These obligations are further complicated by the complex web of data compliance pipelines that connect fragmented data sources across cloud, on-premises, and hybrid environments.</p>
                <h3>The Challenge of Fragmented Data Compliance Pipelines and Manual Processes</h3>
                <p>Organizations now face the dual challenge of managing fragmented data compliance pipelines and disjointed manual compliance processes. Siloed tools and disparate manual audits create blind spots across the <a
                    href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Information_technology"
                    target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">IT</a> environment, making it difficult to achieve end-to-end visibility into data flows and compliance pipeline status. This fragmentation impedes timely detection and response to potential compliance violations, while also increasing operational overhead during intensive audit cycles. The evolving nature of both regulatory demands and data infrastructure necessitates a more dynamic approach to compliance pipeline monitoring and reporting.</p>
                                <h3>The Need for a Unified, Automated Data Compliance Pipeline Approach</h3>
                                <p>Given the increasing complexity of data compliance pipelines, financial institutions require a unified approach capable of orchestrating and automating compliance pipeline monitoring across diverse data sources and environments. This approach must deliver real-time insights into control effectiveness, enable rapid detection of deviations from policy, and provide reliable, comprehensive reporting. Solutions such as the Splunk Solution Accelerator address these needs by centralizing compliance pipeline data, automating continuous monitoring of key controls, and streamlining audit preparation for major frameworks like <a href="https://www.pcisecuritystandards.org/"
                                        target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">PCI DSS</a>
                                    and <a
                                        href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Financial_services"
                                        target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">financial services</a> industry-specific requirements. By leveraging a platform that unifies and automates compliance pipelines, organizations can significantly reduce risk, increase operational efficiency, and confidently demonstrate continuous compliance in the face of ever-changing regulatory and data landscape complexities.</p>
                            </td>
                            <td style="width: 30%; vertical-align: top; padding: 15px;">
                                <img width="2500" usemap="#nav_banner_map"
                                    src="/static/app/Data_Compliance/FSI_Data_Compliance_shield.jpg" />
                            </td>
                        </tr>
                    </table>
                </ul>
                <h1>
                    <!-- Placeholder: Update icon -->
                    <img width="45" src="/static/app/Data_Compliance/SA_image_icon_target.png" />
                    <b>The Role of Assets and Identities in Data Compliance</b>
                </h1>
                <ul>
                    <h2>Achieving Auditability Through Asset and Identity Monitoring</h2>
                    <table>
                        <tr>
                            <td>
                                <h3>Navigating Compliance Through Asset and Identity Intelligence</h3>
                                <p>At the core of navigating this complex compliance landscape lies
                                    the crucial interplay between assets and identities. In response
                                    to increasing regulation, financial institutions are recognizing
                                    the necessity of making asset and identity intelligence the
                                    cornerstone of their compliance strategy. Several compelling
                                    forces are propelling this shift, including regulatory scrutiny
                                    focused on data governance and access controls, the steady
                                    proliferation of digital assets and services, the rise of more
                                    sophisticated cyber threats targeting financial data and
                                    systems, and the increasing costs associated with compliance
                                    failures.</p>

                                <h3>Defining Assets and Identities in Compliance</h3>
                                <p>Assets encompass the vital information and systems underpinning
                                    business operations. This ranges from sensitive customer data,
                                    financial instruments, and <a
                                        href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Information_technology"
                                        target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">IT</a>
                                    infrastructure to critical third-party services. Complementing
                                    this are identities, the detailed sets of information that
                                    uniquely identify individuals and accounts. This includes
                                    employees, customers, and partners, but also extends to
                                    automated systems and <a
                                        href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/API" target="_blank"
                                        rel="noopener noreferrer">APIs</a>, which are increasingly
                                    interacting with sensitive data. Understanding and tracking the
                                    relationship between these assets and the identities that access
                                    them is fundamental to data compliance.</p>

                                <h3>Leveraging Splunk for Asset and Identity Monitoring</h3>
                                <p>The imperative for centralized monitoring and robust auditability
                                    is paramount, and it's here that focusing on assets and
                                    identities within a platform like Splunk becomes essential.
                                    Splunk enables organizations to collect and analyze data
                                    precisely relevant to specific compliance requirements related
                                    to both assets and identities. This includes meticulously
                                    tracking access to sensitive cardholder data (a critical asset
                                    under <a href="https://www.pcisecuritystandards.org/"
                                        target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">PCI DSS</a>
                                    Requirement 7) and monitoring user activity (related to
                                    identities) for <a
                                        href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Financial_services"
                                        target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">FSI</a> audit
                                    trails. By providing a single, authoritative source of truth for
                                    all relevant data, Splunk empowers organizations to effectively
                                    monitor configurations (related to assets under <a
                                        href="https://www.pcisecuritystandards.org/" target="_blank"
                                        rel="noopener noreferrer">PCI DSS</a> Requirement 2) and
                                    identify potential issues related to who is accessing what,
                                    when, and why. This proactive approach to asset and identity
                                    intelligence, facilitated by Splunk, is key to navigating the
                                    complexities of modern data compliance.</p>
                            </td>
                            <td style="width: 30%; vertical-align: top; padding: 15px;">
                                <img width="2500" usemap="#nav_banner_map"
                                    src="/static/app/Data_Compliance/compliance.jpg" />
                            </td>
                        </tr>
                    </table>
                </ul>

                <hr />
                <h1>
                    <img width="45" src="/static/app/Data_Compliance/SA_image_icon_bulb.png" />
                    <b>HELPFUL RESOURCES</b>
                </h1>
                <ul>
                    <ul>
                        <h2>
                            <a
                                href="https://www.splunk.com/en_us/form/five-steps-to-greater-digital-resilience.html"
                                target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">
                                <b>5 Steps to Greater Digital Resilience</b>
                            </a>
                        </h2>
                        <p>In this guide, we outline five strategies that can increase the digital
                            resilience of your organization.</p>
                        <h2>
                            <a
                                href="https://www.splunk.com/en_us/form/future-proof-compliance-for-financial-services.html"
                                target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">
                                <b>Future-Proof Compliance Guide for Financial Services</b>
                            </a>
                        </h2>
                        <p>Discover how Splunk helps financial services organizations adapt to
                            compliance challenges with AI, automation, and data-driven insights to
                            build operational resilience.</p>
                        <h2>
                            <a
                                href="https://lantern.splunk.com/Splunk_Platform/Use_Cases/Financial_Services_and_Insurance"
                                target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">
                                <b>Splunk for Financial Services and Insurance</b>
                            </a>
                        </h2>
                        <p>Explore how Splunk assists <a
                                href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Financial_services"
                                target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">FSI</a> organizations with
                            regulatory compliance, fraud detection, operational resilience, and
                            security monitoring within the unique context of the financial industry.</p>

                        <h2>
                            <a
                                href="https://lantern.splunk.com/Security/UCE/Foundational_Visibility/Compliance"
                                target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">
                                <b>Splunk Lantern for Compliance Use Cases</b>
                            </a>
                        </h2>
                        <p>Discover how Splunk helps organizations meet various compliance mandates.
                            Find guidance on collecting relevant data, implementing monitoring
                            searches, and building dashboards for specific regulations.</p>

                        <h1>
                            <b>Splunk resources for PCI Compliance</b>
                        </h1>
                        <p>Learn how Splunk addresses specific <a
                                href="https://www.pcisecuritystandards.org/" target="_blank"
                                rel="noopener noreferrer">PCI DSS</a> requirements through log
                            collection, monitoring, alerting, and reporting. Find technical examples
                            and best practices for using Splunk in your <a
                                href="https://www.pcisecuritystandards.org/glossary/cardholder-data-environment-cde/"
                                target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Cardholder Data
                                Environment
                                (CDE)</a>.</p>

                        <h2>
                            <a
                                href="https://lantern.splunk.com/Security/UCE/Foundational_Visibility/Compliance/Using_the_Splunk_App_for_PCI_Compliance"
                                target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">
                                <b>Splunk for PCI Compliance</b>
                            </a>
                        </h2>
                        <p>This article provides an introduction to the Splunk App for PCI
                            Compliance, showing you how to use it to monitor and assess <a
                                href="https://www.pcisecuritystandards.org/" target="_blank"
                                rel="noopener noreferrer">PCI DSS</a> requirements while
                            continuously validating.</p>
                        <h2>
                            <a
                                href="https://splunkbase.splunk.com/app/1143" target="_blank"
                                rel="noopener noreferrer">
                                <b>Splunk App for PCI Compliance - Splunk Enterprise</b>
                            </a>
                        </h2>
                        <p>The Splunk App for PCI Compliance (for <a
                                href="https://www.splunk.com/en_us/software/splunk-enterprise.html"
                                target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Splunk Enterprise</a>) is
                            a Splunk developed and supported App designed to help organizations meet <a
                                href="https://www.pcisecuritystandards.org/" target="_blank"
                                rel="noopener noreferrer">PCI DSS</a> 4.0 requirements.</p>
                        <h2>
                            <a
                                href="https://splunkbase.splunk.com/app/2897" target="_blank"
                                rel="noopener noreferrer">
                                <b>Splunk App for PCI Compliance - Splunk Enterprise Security</b>
                            </a>
                        </h2>
                        <p>The Splunk App for PCI Compliance (for <a
                                href="https://www.splunk.com/en_us/software/enterprise-security.html"
                                target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Splunk Enterprise Security</a>)
                            is a Splunk developed and supported App designed to help organizations
                            meet <a href="https://www.pcisecuritystandards.org/" target="_blank"
                                rel="noopener noreferrer">PCI DSS</a> 4.0 requirements.</p>
                    </ul>
                </ul>
            </html>
        </panel>
    </row>
    <!-- WHY SPLUNK FOR COMPLIANCE TAB -->
    <row id="tab_02">
        <panel>
            <html>
                <h1>
                    <img width="45" src="/static/app/Data_Compliance/SA_image_icon_bulb.png" />
                    <b>WHY SPLUNK?</b>
                </h1>
                <ul>
                    <h2>Achieving Continuous Compliance with Data-Driven Insights</h2>
                    <p>Splunk provides a powerful platform to address data compliance challenges by
                        turning machine data into actionable insights for monitoring, auditing, and
                        reporting.</p>
                    <p>Instead of relying on disparate tools and manual checks, Splunk centralizes
                        relevant data, enabling automated monitoring of compliance controls, rapid
                        investigation of potential violations, and streamlined evidence gathering
                        for audits like <a href="https://www.pcisecuritystandards.org/"
                            target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">PCI DSS</a> assessments or <a
                            href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Financial_services" target="_blank"
                            rel="noopener noreferrer">FSI</a> regulatory reviews.</p>

                    <hr />

                    <h2>Key Capabilities for Compliance:</h2>
                    <ul>
                        <li><b>Centralized Data Collection:</b> Ingest logs, configurations, access
                            events, and other relevant data from across your hybrid environment (<a
                                href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/On-premises_software"
                                target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">on-prem</a>, cloud,
                            multi-cloud).</li>
                        <li><b>Continuous Controls Monitoring:</b> Implement searches and alerts to
                            automatically monitor adherence to specific compliance requirements
                            (e.g., password policies, access controls, change management).</li>
                        <li><b>Audit Trail Generation:</b> Maintain comprehensive, searchable logs
                            of user activity, system changes, and data access for audit and
                            investigation purposes.</li>
                        <li><b>Automated Reporting:</b> Generate dashboards and reports tailored to
                            specific compliance frameworks (PCI, <a
                                href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Financial_services"
                                target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">FSI</a>, <a
                                href="https://www.congress.gov/bill/107th-congress/house-bill/3763"
                                target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">SOX</a>, etc.) to
                            demonstrate adherence and simplify audit preparation.</li>
                        <li><b>Rapid Incident Response:</b> Quickly investigate potential compliance
                            breaches or security incidents impacting regulated data.</li>
                    </ul>

                    <hr />

                    <h2>Included Components (Conceptual):</h2>
                    <ul>
                        <li><b>Compliance-Focused Data Models:</b> Structures to normalize data
                            relevant to common compliance controls (e.g., Authentication, Change
                            Management, Network Traffic).</li>
                        <li><b>Technology Add-Ons (<a
                                    href="https://docs.splunk.com/Documentation/AddOns/latest/Overview/AboutSplunkAdd-ons"
                                    target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">TAs</a>):</b> Parsers
                            and configurations to easily ingest data from security devices, servers,
                            applications, and cloud services relevant to compliance.</li>
                        <li><b>Pre-built Searches &amp; Dashboards:</b> Examples targeting specific <a
                                href="https://www.pcisecuritystandards.org/" target="_blank"
                                rel="noopener noreferrer">PCI DSS</a> requirements, <a
                                href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Financial_services"
                                target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">FSI</a> logging standards,
                            or general compliance controls (e.g., Failed Login Monitoring,
                            Privileged User Activity Tracking).</li>
                        <li><b>Compliance Reporting Framework:</b> Templates and examples for
                            generating reports suitable for auditors.</li>
                        <li><b>Alerting Examples:</b> Pre-configured alert templates for common
                            compliance violations (e.g., unauthorized access attempts, critical file
                            modifications).</li>
                    </ul>
                </ul>
            </html>
        </panel>
    </row>
    <!-- REFERENCE ARCH TAB -->
    <row id="tab_03">
        <panel>
            <html tokens="true">
                <h1>
                    <img width="45" src="/static/app/Data_Compliance/SA_image_icon_tool.png" />
                    <b>DATA PIPELINE MANAGEMENT REFERENCE ARCHITECTURE:</b>
                </h1>

                <p>Achieving timely and comprehensive data compliance in the financial services
                    sector requires accommodating a wide array of architectures and disparate
                    data collection methods across numerous applications and systems.</p>

                <img src="/static/app/Data_Compliance/ref_arch.jpg"
                    style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto; width: 66%;" />

                <hr />
                <h1>
                    <img width="45" src="/static/app/Data_Compliance/SA_image_icon_bulb.png" />
                    <b>ADDITIONAL REFERENCES:</b>
                </h1>
                <ul>
                    <p>Achieving timely and comprehensive data compliance in the financial services
                        sector requires accommodating a wide array of architectures and disparate
                        data collection methods across numerous applications and systems.</p>
                    <p>The Data Compliance Pipelines Solutions Accelerator for Financial Services
                        directly
                        addresses these challenges. It offers proven methodologies and pre-built
                        components to accelerate your Splunk deployment, ensuring robust and
                        compliant data ingestion from your complex financial ecosystem to meet
                        regulatory demands more efficiently.</p>
                    <p>Access these valuable resources provided by the accelerator:</p>
                    <ul>
                        <ul>
                            <li><b>
                                    <a
                                        href="https://www.splunk.com/en_us/form/new-rules-of-data-management-for-financial-services.html"
                                        target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Financial services
                                institutions can become data management leaders in the <a
                                            href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Artificial_intelligence"
                                            target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">AI</a> era</a>
                                </b>:
                                Today’s financial institutions contend with vast amounts of data.
                                But they’re exploring strategies to become data management leaders
                                in the <a
                                    href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Artificial_intelligence"
                                    target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">AI</a> era.</li>
                            <li><b>
                                    <a
                                        href="https://www.splunk.com/en_us/form/the-new-rules-of-data-management.html"
                                        target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">The
                                        New Rules of Data Management</a>
                                </b>:
                                Learn how to tame data complexity and drive better cybersecurity and
                                observability outcomes with the new rules of data management.</li>
                            <li><b>
                                    <a
                                        href="https://www.splunk.com/en_us/resources/beyond-compliance-a-better-playbook-for-long-term-digital-resilience-in-financial-services.html"
                                        target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Beyond
                                        Compliance: Financial Services Industry Brief</a>
                                </b>:
                                Explore strategies for long-term digital resilience in financial
                                services that go beyond compliance. Learn how to tackle
                                cybersecurity threats, meet rising customer expectations, and adapt
                                to regulatory changes.</li>
                            <li><b>
                                    <a
                                        href="https://www.splunk.com/en_us/resources/videos/splunk-data-management-pipeline-builder-edge-processor-overview.html"
                                        target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Splunk Data
                                Management Pipeline Builder: <a
                                            href="https://www.splunk.com/en_us/products/edge-processor.html"
                                            target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Edge Processor</a>
                                Overview</a>
                                </b>: Learn how <a
                                    href="https://www.splunk.com/en_us/products/edge-processor.html"
                                    target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Edge Processor</a>
                                helps you transform data at the edge so you can reduce noise,
                                control costs, and ingest data in the exact shape that you need it.</li>
                            <li><b>
                                    <a
                                        href="https://www.splunk.com/en_us/form/five-essentials-for-financial-services-compliance-success.html"
                                        target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Five
                                        Must Have’s for Financial Services Compliance</a>
                                </b>:
                                Discover the five critical capabilities financial services need to
                                ensure compliance, mitigate risks, and thrive in a complex
                                regulatory landscape.</li>
                        </ul>
                    </ul>
                </ul>
            </html>
        </panel>
    </row>
    <!-- Add rows for specific compliance tabs (e.g., id="tab_03" for PCI) if needed -->
    <row id="tab_next">
        <panel>
            <html tokens="true">
                <h1>
                    <img width="45" src="/static/app/Data_Compliance/SA_image_icon_ques.png" />
                    <b>Do you need help? Ask a Data Compliance Expert.</b>
                </h1>
                <ul>
                    <p> Need help implementing compliance monitoring in your environment or
                        tailoring this accelerator to specific regulations like <a
                            href="https://www.pcisecuritystandards.org/" target="_blank"
                            rel="noopener noreferrer">PCI DSS</a> or <a
                            href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Financial_services" target="_blank"
                            rel="noopener noreferrer">FSI</a> requirements? Send us your questions.</p>
                    <ul>
                        <!-- Placeholder: Update Lantern link for THIS accelerator -->
                        <li> For detailed step-by-step instructions on implementing solutions using
                            this Accelerator, visit our <a
                                href="https://lantern.splunk.com/Security/UCE/Foundational_Visibility/Compliance"
                                target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">
                                <b>Solution Accelerator Lantern Page</b>
                            </a>
                            .</li>
                        <!-- Placeholder: Update expertCode -->
                        <li> To expedite implementation with professional services, please reach out
                            to our sales team by clicking <a
                                href="https://www.splunk.com/en_us/ask-an-expert.html?expertCode=Data_Compliance_expert_code"
                                target="_ask_expert">
                                <b>Contact Us</b>
                            </a>.</li>
                        <li> If you need immediate assistance, explore our community forum, <a
                                href="http://answers.splunk.com/" target="_blank"
                                rel="noopener noreferrer">
                                <b>Splunk Answers</b>
                            </a>.</li>
                    </ul>
                    <!-- Placeholder: Update bullet image if needed -->
                    <img src="/static/app/Data_Compliance/SA_image_bullet_03.png" />
                    <!-- Placeholder: Update expertCode -->
                    <a
                        href="https://www.splunk.com/en_us/ask-an-expert.html?expertCode=Data_Compliance_expert_code"
                        class="btn" target="_ask_expert">Contact Us</a>
                </ul>
                <table>
                    <tr>
                        <td>
                            <div class="col-sm-6 col-lg-5 col-lg-offset-1 col-md-offset-1 photo-box">
                                <!-- Optional: Add relevant image or leave empty -->
                            </div>
                        </td>
                    </tr>
                </table>
            </html>
        </panel>
    </row>
</dashboard>