<dashboard version="1.1" theme="light" script="tabs.js" stylesheet="tabs.css">
   <label>Regional Compliance Regulations</label>

   <label>Introduction to Data Compliance Regulations</label>
   <description>Navigating the complex and evolving global data compliance landscape impacting
      financial services organizations.</description>
   <row>
      <panel>
         <html>
            <h1>
               <!-- Placeholder: Update icon path -->
               <img width="40"
                  src="/static/app/Data_Compliance_Pipelines/SA_image_icon_target.png" />
               <b>INTRODUCTION</b>
            </h1>
            <ul>
               <!-- Updated Introduction Text -->
               <p>The global landscape of data compliance regulations has expanded dramatically,
                  reflecting a growing international consensus on the importance of protecting
                  sensitive information and ensuring responsible data stewardship. Governments and
                  regulatory bodies worldwide are actively implementing and enforcing stringent
                  rules aimed at safeguarding individual privacy, bolstering cybersecurity defenses,
                  and preventing illicit activities. While the fundamental objectives—such as
                  requiring consent for data collection, ensuring data security, and providing
                  individuals with rights over their information—are often similar, the sheer volume
                  and breadth of these mandates mean that organizations must navigate a complex web
                  of obligations that impact nearly every business function.</p>
               <p>Adding to this complexity is the significant variation in how these regulations
                  are defined and implemented across different jurisdictions. Rather than a single
                  global standard, companies must contend with distinct regional and national
                  frameworks. Europe has the <a href="https://gdpr-info.eu/" target="_blank"
                     rel="noopener noreferrer">GDPR</a>, the United States has federal laws like <a
                     href="https://ftc.gov/business-guidance/privacy-security/gramm-leach-bliley-act" target="_blank"
                     rel="noopener noreferrer">GLBA</a> and state-specific rules like <a
                     href="https://oag.ca.gov/privacy/ccpa" target="_blank"
                     rel="noopener noreferrer">CCPA</a>,and <a href="https://thecpra.org/"
                     target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">CPRA</a>, and many other countries
                  are developing their own unique data protection legislation. This fragmentation
                  means that an organization operating across borders cannot apply a
                  one-size-fits-all approach but must instead understand and comply with the
                  specific requirements of every region where they collect, process, or store data,
                  making robust, adaptable compliance strategies essential.</p>
            </ul>
         </html>
      </panel>
   </row>
   <row id="tabs">
      <panel>
         <html>
            <p>
               <ul id="tabs" class="nav nav-tabs">
                  <li>
                     <!-- Placeholder: Update nav button image -->
                     <img width="200"
                        src="/static/app/Data_Compliance_Pipelines/SA_image_icon_navi_gr_button.png" />
                  </li>
                  <li class="active">
                     <a href="#" class="toggle-tab" data-toggle="tab" data-elements="tab_objective">1
                        | OBJECTIVE</a>
                  </li>
                  <li>
                     <a href="#" class="toggle-tab" data-toggle="tab" data-elements="tab_global">2 |
                        GLOBAL REGULATIONS</a>
                  </li>
                  <li>
                     <a href="#" class="toggle-tab" data-toggle="tab" data-elements="tab_amer">3 |
                        AMER REGULATIONS</a>
                  </li>
                  <li>
                     <a href="#" class="toggle-tab" data-toggle="tab" data-elements="tab_emea">4 |
                        EMEA REGULATIONS</a>
                  </li>
                  <li>
                     <a href="#" class="toggle-tab" data-toggle="tab" data-elements="tab_apjc">5 |
                        APJC REGULATIONS</a>
                  </li>
                  <li>
                     <a href="#" class="toggle-tab" data-toggle="tab" data-elements="tab_anz">6 |
                        A/NZ REGULATIONS</a>
                  </li>
               </ul>
            </p>
         </html>
      </panel>
   </row>
   <row id="tab_objective">
      <panel>
         <html>
            <ul>
               <h1>
                  <!-- Placeholder: Update icon path -->
                  <img width="35"
                     src="/static/app/Data_Compliance_Pipelines/SA_image_icon_target.png" />
                  <b>OBJECTIVE:</b>
               </h1>
               <!-- Updated Objective Text -->
               <p>In light of the widespread and increasingly complex global landscape of data
                  compliance regulations, the primary objective of data compliance initiatives is to
                  ensure stringent adherence to the vast and varied body of relevant laws,
                  regulations, industry standards, and internal policies governing data security and
                  privacy. This necessitates the meticulous implementation and maintenance of
                  appropriate technical and organizational controls designed to protect sensitive
                  information - such as customer <a
                     href="https://csrc.nist.gov/glossary/term/personally_identifiable_information"
                     target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">PII</a>, financial data, and
                  cardholder data - and the crucial ability to effectively demonstrate this
                  adherence to auditors and regulators across different jurisdictions.</p>
               <p>Achieving this overarching objective involves several key goals, driven by the
                  need to navigate diverse and evolving mandates: <ul>
                     <ul>
                        <li>
                           <b>Meeting Diverse Regulatory Requirements:</b> Satisfying the specific
                  mandates from numerous frameworks operating across different regions and sectors,
                  including <a href="https://www.pcisecuritystandards.org/" target="_blank"
                              rel="noopener noreferrer">PCI DSS</a> (e.g., Requirement 10 for
                  logging, Requirement 7 for access control), <a href="https://gdpr-info.eu/"
                              target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">GDPR</a> (e.g., data subject
                  rights, breach notification), <a
                              href="https://www.congress.gov/bill/107th-congress/house-bill/3763"
                              target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">SOX</a> (financial reporting
                  controls), and
                  a multitude of varied <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Financial_services"
                              target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">FSI</a> regulations
                  applicable in specific markets.</li>
                        <li>
                           <b>Protecting Sensitive Data:</b> Implementing robust security controls
                  (encryption, access management, vulnerability management) critical for preventing
                  data breaches and unauthorized access, as required by nearly all data protection
                  regulations.</li>
                        <li>
                           <b>Ensuring Data Privacy:</b> Managing data according to global privacy
                  principles, encompassing consent management, purpose limitation, data
                  minimization, and honoring data subject rights (like <a
                              href="https://gdpr.eu/article-15-right-of-access-by-the-data-subject/"
                              target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">DSARs</a>) as defined by
                  regulations like <a href="https://gdpr-info.eu/" target="_blank"
                              rel="noopener noreferrer">GDPR</a> and <a
                              href="https://oag.ca.gov/privacy/ccpa" target="_blank"
                              rel="noopener noreferrer">CCPA</a>.</li>
                        <li>
                           <b>Streamlining Audits:</b> Significantly reducing the effort and cost
                  associated with compliance audits by centralizing evidence, automating control
                  monitoring across diverse systems, and simplifying reporting for different
                  regulatory bodies.</li>
                        <li>
                           <b>Managing Risk:</b> Proactively identifying and mitigating compliance
                  risks related to data handling, security posture across varied environments, and
                  interactions with third-party vendors governed by numerous regulations.</li>
                        <li>
                           <b>Building Trust:</b> Demonstrating a clear and verifiable commitment to
                  data protection and compliance with regional regulations, thereby enhancing
                  customer confidence and solidifying brand reputation in every market served.</li>
                     </ul>
                  </ul>
               </p>
               <p>An effective data compliance program, especially in this fragmented regulatory
                  environment, must leverage continuous monitoring and data analysis to provide
                  ongoing assurance that controls are working as intended. This capability allows
                  the organization to quickly identify and respond to potential issues across its
                  global operations, minimizing financial, legal, and reputational damage regardless
                  of the specific regulation involved.</p>
            </ul>

            <hr width="100%" />
            <ul>
               <h1>
                  <!-- Placeholder: Update icon path -->
                  <img width="35"
                     src="/static/app/Data_Compliance_Pipelines/SA_image_icon_target.png" />
                  <b>PREREQUISITES: Data Inputs for Global Compliance Visibility</b>
               </h1>
               <!-- Updated Prerequisites Text -->
               <p>To effectively navigate the complex, fragmented, and regionally diverse data
                  compliance landscape discussed in the introduction, gaining comprehensive
                  visibility and enabling the crucial interplay between assets and identities
                  requires the ingestion and analysis of specific data types from across your IT
                  environment. These data sources serve as the fundamental building blocks,
                  providing the necessary evidence and context to monitor controls, detect
                  deviations, and generate required audit trails across various global and regional
                  regulatory mandates.</p>
               <p>While specific requirements vary by regulation (<a href="https://gdpr-info.eu/"
                     target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">GDPR</a>, <a
                     href="https://www.pcisecuritystandards.org/" target="_blank"
                     rel="noopener noreferrer">PCI DSS</a>, <a
                     href="https://www.congress.gov/bill/107th-congress/house-bill/3763"
                     target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">SOX</a>, <a
                     href="https://oag.ca.gov/privacy/ccpa" target="_blank"
                     rel="noopener noreferrer">CCPA</a>, etc.), the following categories of data are
                  typically required inputs for comprehensive data compliance pipelines monitoring and
                  auditing within this Solution Accelerator for Data Compliance Pipelines:</p>
               <ul>
                  <h3>User &amp; System Activity Logs</h3>
                  <ul>
                     <li>
                        <b>Authentication &amp; Access Logs:</b> Essential for monitoring identity
                        activity and access to sensitive assets. System, application, database, and <a
                           href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Virtual_private_network"
                           target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">VPN</a> logs showing user
                        logins (success/failure), access attempts to sensitive resources, and
                        privilege escalations are critical for audit trails required globally.
                        (e.g., Windows Security Events, Linux auth logs, Active Directory logs,
                        Cloud <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Identity_management"
                           target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">IAM</a> logs). </li>
                     <li>
                        <b>Operating System Logs:</b> Provide granular audit trails at the <a
                           href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Operating_system" target="_blank"
                           rel="noopener noreferrer">OS</a> level (an asset), capturing system
                        events, process execution, and critical errors relevant to compliance and
                        security across your infrastructure. (e.g., Windows Event Logs, Linux
                        syslog). </li>
                     <li>
                        <b>Database Audit Logs:</b> Crucial for monitoring access to sensitive data
                        (an asset) within databases and tracking administrative actions and schema
                        changes, vital for data integrity and privacy regulations worldwide. </li>
                     <li>
                        <b>Cloud Infrastructure Logs:</b> Provide audit trails for cloud assets and
                        identities, detailing API calls, resource modifications, security group
                        changes, and access events within cloud environments, necessary for
                        compliance as cloud adoption grows globally. (e.g., <a
                           href="https://aws.amazon.com/cloudtrail/" target="_blank"
                           rel="noopener noreferrer">AWS CloudTrail</a>, <a
                           href="https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/azure-monitor/essentials/activity-log"
                           target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Azure Activity Log</a>, <a
                           href="https://cloud.google.com/logging/docs/audit" target="_blank"
                           rel="noopener noreferrer">GCP Audit Logs</a>). </li>
                  </ul>
                  <h3>Configuration &amp; Asset State Logs</h3>
                  <ul>
                     <li>
                        <b>Change Management Logs:</b> Key for tracking modifications to critical
                        assets and configurations that could impact security posture and compliance
                        mandates related to system integrity and controls. Records of changes to
                        system configurations, firewall rules, user permissions, and application
                        code are necessary. (e.g., Config management tool logs, <a
                           href="https://git-scm.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Git</a>
                        logs, <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Operating_system"
                           target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">OS</a> change logs). </li>
                     <li>
                        <b>Endpoint Security Logs:</b> Offer insights into the security status of
                        endpoints (assets) and potential threats impacting data.
                        Antivirus/anti-malware alerts, host-based intrusion detection events, file
                        integrity monitoring alerts, and <a
                           href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Data_loss_prevention_software"
                           target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">DLP</a> events are important
                        for compliance monitoring and incident response globally. </li>
                     <li>
                        <b>Vulnerability Scan Data</b> (Optional but Recommended): Results from
                        vulnerability scanners identifying weaknesses in systems (assets) that could
                        lead to non-compliance or breaches, a common requirement across security
                        frameworks. </li>
                  </ul>
                  <h3>Network &amp; Data Flow Logs</h3>
                  <ul>
                     <li>
                        <b>Network Activity Logs:</b> Provide visibility into the flow of data (a
                        key asset) and potential policy violations across the network. Firewall,
                        proxy, <a
                           href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/news/understanding-intrusion-detection-systems-ids"
                           target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">IDS/IPS</a>, and network flow
                        data showing traffic patterns, connection attempts, and potential policy
                        violations are valuable for monitoring data exfiltration and network
                        security controls. </li>
                  </ul>
                  <h3>Asset &amp; Identity Context Data</h3>
                  <ul>
                     <li>
                        <b>Asset &amp; Identity Data</b> (Optional but Highly Recommended): Explicit
                        information correlating systems/IPs to owners/functions (assets) and users
                        to roles/permissions (identities). While partially inferred from other logs,
                        explicit data significantly enhances the ability to analyze compliance
                        against specific roles, responsibilities, and critical assets, crucial in a
                        complex organizational and regulatory landscape. </li>
                  </ul>
               </ul>
               <p>Centralizing and correlating these diverse data inputs is fundamental to the
                  Solution Accelerator for Data Compliance Pipelines's ability to provide the
                  necessary comprehensive visibility
                  for compliance across various regulations and to effectively monitor the
                  interactions between assets and identities in a globally distributed environment.</p>
            </ul>
         </html>
      </panel>
   </row>
   <row id="tab_global">
      <panel>
         <html>
            <ul>
               <h1>
                  <!-- Placeholder: Update icon path -->
                  <img width="35"
                     src="/static/app/Data_Compliance_Pipelines/SA_image_icon_target.png" />
                  <b>GLOBAL REGULATIONS</b>
               </h1>
               <table>
                  <tr>
                     <td>
                        <ul>
                           <li>
                              <p><b>KYC (Know Your Customer) &amp; AML/CFT (Anti-Money Laundering /
                                 Counter-Terrorist Financing):</b> These are sets of international
                                 standards and national laws designed to prevent financial
                                 institutions from being used for money laundering, terrorist
                                 financing, and other illicit financial activities. <a
                                    href="https://www.fatf-gafi.org/en/glossary/know-your-customer-customer-due-diligence.html"
                                    target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">KYC</a> involves
                                 verifying the identity of customers and assessing their risk
                                 profiles, while <a
                                    href="https://www.fatf-gafi.org/en/topics/anti-money-laundering-and-counter-terrorist-financing.html"
                                    target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">AML/CFT</a>
                                 encompasses broader measures including transaction monitoring,
                                 reporting suspicious activities, and implementing robust internal
                                 controls.</p>
                              <p><b>In Brief:</b> <a
                                    href="https://www.fatf-gafi.org/en/glossary/know-your-customer-customer-due-diligence.html"
                                    target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">KYC</a> and <a
                                    href="https://www.fatf-gafi.org/en/topics/anti-money-laundering-and-counter-terrorist-financing.html"
                                    target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">AML/CFT</a>
                                 regulations aim to prevent financial crime by requiring financial
                                 institutions to verify customer identity, understand their
                                 activities, and monitor transactions.</p>
                           </li>
                           <li>
                              <p><b>Cross-Border Data Transfer Rules:</b> These rules, often part of
                                 broader data privacy laws (like <a href="https://gdpr-info.eu/"
                                    target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">GDPR</a>'s transfer
                                 mechanisms) or specific international agreements, dictate the
                                 conditions under which personal and sensitive financial data can be
                                 legally moved from one country to another. They aim to ensure that
                                 data remains protected even when it leaves its original
                                 jurisdiction, often requiring adequacy decisions, standard
                                 contractual clauses, or other safeguards.</p>
                              <p><b>In Brief:</b> <a
                                    href="https://www.unodc.org/e4j/en/cybercrime/module-10/key-issues/cross-border-data-flows.html"
                                    target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Cross-Border Data
                                 Transfer Rules</a> are international agreements and national laws
                                 governing how sensitive personal and financial data can be moved
                                 legally across international boundaries.</p>
                           </li>
                           <li>
                              <p><b>T+1 Settlement:</b> <a
                                    href="https://www.dtcc.com/settlement-central/t-plus-1"
                                    target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">T+1 Settlement</a>
                                 refers to a market convention where security trades are settled one
                                 business day after the trade date (T). This shift from longer
                                 settlement cycles (like T+2) aims to reduce counterparty risk,
                                 credit risk, and market risk by decreasing the time between trade
                                 execution and final settlement, requiring faster data processing,
                                 reconciliation, and communication among market participants.</p>
                              <p><b>In Brief:</b> <a
                                    href="https://www.dtcc.com/settlement-central/t-plus-1"
                                    target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">T+1 Settlement</a>
                                 aims to reduce market risk by shortening the time between a
                                 securities trade and its settlement to one business day, requiring
                                 faster data processing and exchange.</p>
                           </li>
                        </ul>
                     </td>
                     <td style="width: 30%; vertical-align: top; padding: 15px;">
                        <!-- Placeholder: Update image path -->
                        <img width="2500" src="/static/app/Data_Compliance_Pipelines/global.png" />
                     </td>
                  </tr>
               </table>
            </ul>
         </html>
      </panel>
   </row>
   <row id="tab_amer">
      <panel>
         <html>
            <ul>
               <h1>
                  <!-- Placeholder: Update icon path -->
                  <img width="35"
                     src="/static/app/Data_Compliance_Pipelines/SA_image_icon_target.png" />
                  <b>AMER REGULATIONS</b>
               </h1>
               <table>
                  <tr>
                     <td>
                        <ul>
                           <li>
                              <p><b>Sarbanes-Oxley Act (SOX):</b> Enacted in the United States, <a
                                    href="https://www.congress.gov/bill/107th-congress/house-bill/3763"
                                    target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">SOX</a> is a federal
                                 law that mandates strict reforms to improve financial disclosures
                                 from corporations and prevent accounting fraud. It holds senior
                                 executives responsible for the accuracy of financial reports and
                                 requires robust internal controls over financial reporting (<a
                                    href="https://pcaobus.org/oversight/standards/auditing-standards/details/AS2201"
                                    target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">ICFR</a>), including
                                 controls over the IT systems and data that support these reports.</p>
                              <p><b>In Brief:</b> <a
                                    href="https://www.congress.gov/bill/107th-congress/house-bill/3763"
                                    target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">SOX</a> requires
                                 public companies to establish and maintain internal controls over
                                 financial reporting and the underlying data and systems to prevent
                                 fraud and errors, impacting data integrity and retention.</p>
                           </li>
                           <li>
                              <p><b>Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA):</b> Also known as the Financial
                                 Services Modernization Act of 1999, <a
                                    href="https://www.ftc.gov/business-guidance/privacy-security/gramm-leach-bliley-act"
                                    target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">GLBA</a> is a U.S.
                                 federal law that requires financial institutions to explain their
                                 information-sharing practices to their customers and to safeguard
                                 sensitive customer data. It includes provisions for privacy notices
                                 and the development of a comprehensive information security
                                 program.</p>
                              <p><b>In Brief:</b> <a
                                    href="https://www.ftc.gov/business-guidance/privacy-security/gramm-leach-bliley-act"
                                    target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">GLBA</a> mandates that
                                 financial institutions protect the privacy and security of consumer
                                 financial information through various administrative, technical,
                                 and physical safeguards.</p>
                           </li>
                           <li>
                              <p><b>California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA) &amp; California Privacy
                                 Rights Act (<a href="https://thecpra.org/" target="_blank"
                                       rel="noopener noreferrer">CPRA</a>):</b> The <a
                                    href="https://oag.ca.gov/privacy/ccpa" target="_blank"
                                    rel="noopener noreferrer">CCPA</a>, as amended by the <a
                                    href="https://thecpra.org/" target="_blank"
                                    rel="noopener noreferrer">CPRA</a>, grants California consumers
                                 comprehensive privacy rights, including the right to know what
                                 personal information is collected, the right to delete it, and the
                                 right to opt-out of its sale or sharing. It applies to businesses
                                 that collect personal information of California residents and meet
                                 certain revenue or data processing thresholds.</p>
                              <p><b>In Brief:</b> <a href="https://oag.ca.gov/privacy/ccpa"
                                    target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">CCPA</a>,and <a
                                    href="https://thecpra.org/" target="_blank"
                                    rel="noopener noreferrer">CPRA</a> grant California consumers
                                 specific rights regarding their personal information collected by
                                 businesses, including access, deletion, and the right to opt-out of
                                 sale or sharing.</p>
                           </li>
                           <li>
                              <p><b>23 NYCRR 500:</b> This regulation from the <a
                                    href="https://www.dfs.ny.gov/" target="_blank"
                                    rel="noopener noreferrer">New York State
                                    Department of Financial Services (NYDFS)</a> establishes
                                 cybersecurity requirements for all financial services companies
                                 operating under <a href="https://www.dfs.ny.gov/" target="_blank"
                                    rel="noopener noreferrer">NYDFS</a> licensure. It mandates the
                                 development and maintenance of a cybersecurity program designed to
                                 protect the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of
                                 information systems.</p>
                              <p><b>In Brief:</b> <a
                                    href="https://www.dfs.ny.gov/industry_guidance/cybersecurity"
                                    target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">23 NYCRR 500</a> is
                                 New York State's cybersecurity regulation requiring financial
                                 services companies licensed or operating in New York to implement
                                 and maintain specific cybersecurity programs and controls.</p>
                           </li>
                           <li>
                              <p><b><a href="https://www.pcisecuritystandards.org/" target="_blank"
                                       rel="noopener noreferrer">PCI DSS</a> (Payment Card Industry
                                 Data Security Standard):</b> PCI DSS is a global information
                                 security standard applicable to all entities that store, process,
                                 or transmit cardholder data. Developed and managed by the PCI
                                 Security Standards Council, it provides a baseline of technical and
                                 operational requirements designed to protect card data and reduce
                                 credit card fraud.</p>
                              <p><b>In Brief:</b> <a href="https://www.pcisecuritystandards.org/"
                                    target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">PCI DSS</a> is a set
                                 of security standards designed to ensure that all companies that
                                 accept, process, store, or transmit credit card information
                                 maintain a secure environment through specific technical and
                                 operational requirements.</p>
                           </li>
                        </ul>
                     </td>
                     <td style="width: 30%; vertical-align: top; padding: 15px;">
                        <!-- Placeholder: Update image path -->
                        <img width="2500" src="/static/app/Data_Compliance_Pipelines/amer.png" />
                     </td>
                  </tr>
               </table>
            </ul>
         </html>
      </panel>
   </row>
   <row id="tab_emea">
      <panel>
         <html>
            <ul>
               <h1>
                  <!-- Placeholder: Update icon path -->
                  <img width="35"
                     src="/static/app/Data_Compliance_Pipelines/SA_image_icon_target.png" />
                  <b>EMEA REGULATIONS</b>
               </h1>
               <table>
                  <tr>
                     <td>
                        <ul>
                           <li>
                              <p><b><a href="https://gdpr-info.eu/" target="_blank"
                                       rel="noopener noreferrer">GDPR</a> (General Data Protection
                                 Regulation):</b> The <a href="https://gdpr-info.eu/"
                                    target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">GDPR</a> is a landmark
                                 regulation in EU law on data protection and privacy for all
                                 individuals within the <a
                                    href="https://european-union.europa.eu/index_en" target="_blank"
                                    rel="noopener noreferrer">European Union</a> and the <a
                                    href="https://www.efta.int/eea/eea-agreement" target="_blank"
                                    rel="noopener noreferrer">European Economic
                                    Area</a>. It also addresses the transfer of personal data
                                 outside the <a href="https://european-union.europa.eu/index_en"
                                    target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">EU</a> and <a
                                    href="https://www.efta.int/eea/eea-agreement" target="_blank"
                                    rel="noopener noreferrer">EEA</a> areas. It imposes strict
                                 obligations on organizations regarding the collection, processing,
                                 storage, and security of personal data, and grants individuals
                                 significant rights over their data.</p>
                              <p><b>In Brief:</b> <a href="https://gdpr-info.eu/" target="_blank"
                                    rel="noopener noreferrer">GDPR</a> is a comprehensive <a
                                    href="https://european-union.europa.eu/index_en" target="_blank"
                                    rel="noopener noreferrer">EU</a> regulation setting strict rules
                                 for processing personal data of individuals within the <a
                                    href="https://european-union.europa.eu/index_en" target="_blank"
                                    rel="noopener noreferrer">EU</a>, granting them extensive rights
                                 over their data, including consent, access, and erasure.</p>
                           </li>
                           <li>
                              <p><b>DORA (Digital Operational Resilience Act):</b> <a
                                    href="https://eur-lex.europa.eu/eli/reg/2022/2554/oj"
                                    target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">DORA</a> is an <a
                                    href="https://european-union.europa.eu/index_en" target="_blank"
                                    rel="noopener noreferrer">EU</a> regulation aimed at harmonizing
                                 and strengthening the digital operational resilience of financial
                                 entities such as banks, insurance companies, and investment firms,
                                 as well as critical <a
                                    href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Information_and_communications_technology"
                                    target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">ICT</a> third-party
                                 service providers. It sets requirements concerning <a
                                    href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Information_and_communications_technology"
                                    target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">ICT</a> risk
                                 management, incident reporting, resilience testing, and third-party
                                 risk management.</p>
                              <p><b>In Brief:</b> <a
                                    href="https://eur-lex.europa.eu/eli/reg/2022/2554/oj"
                                    target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">DORA</a> is an <a
                                    href="https://european-union.europa.eu/index_en" target="_blank"
                                    rel="noopener noreferrer">EU</a> regulation focused on
                                 strengthening the IT security and operational resilience of
                                 financial entities and critical third parties that provide <a
                                    href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Information_and_communications_technology"
                                    target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">ICT</a> services to
                                 them.</p>
                           </li>
                           <li>
                              <p><b>Bank of England (BoE) Rules and Guidance / FCA &amp; PRA
                                 Requirements (UK):</b> In the <a href="https://www.gov.uk/"
                                    target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">United Kingdom</a>,
                                 the <a href="https://www.bankofengland.co.uk/" target="_blank"
                                    rel="noopener noreferrer">Bank of England</a>, along with the <a
                                    href="https://www.fca.org.uk/" target="_blank"
                                    rel="noopener noreferrer">Financial Conduct Authority (FCA)</a>
                                 and the <a
                                    href="https://www.bankofengland.co.uk/prudential-regulation"
                                    target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Prudential
                                    Regulation Authority (PRA)</a>, sets forth specific rules,
                                 guidance, and supervisory expectations for financial institutions.
                                 These cover a wide range of areas including operational resilience,
                                 cybersecurity, data security, outsourcing, and conduct, aiming to
                                 ensure financial stability and consumer protection.</p>
                              <p><b>In Brief:</b> <a href="https://www.gov.uk/" target="_blank"
                                    rel="noopener noreferrer">UK</a> financial regulators issue
                                 specific rules and guidance covering operational resilience,
                                 cybersecurity, and data security to ensure the stability and
                                 integrity of the <a href="https://www.gov.uk/" target="_blank"
                                    rel="noopener noreferrer">UK</a> financial system.</p>
                           </li>
                           <li>
                              <p><b>BaFin Requirements (Germany):</b> Germany's <a
                                    href="https://www.bafin.de/EN/Homepage/homepage_node.html"
                                    target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Federal Financial
                                 Supervisory Authority (BaFin)</a> issues circulars and guidelines,
                                 such as <a
                                    href="https://www.bafin.de/SharedDocs/Downloads/EN/Rundschreiben/dl_rs_1710_bait_en.html"
                                    target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">BAIT (Banking
                                 Supervisory Requirements for IT)</a> and <a
                                    href="https://www.bafin.de/SharedDocs/Downloads/EN/Rundschreiben/dl_rs_1910_kait_en.html"
                                    target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">KAIT (Capital
                                 Management Supervisory Requirements for IT)</a>, which specify
                                 requirements for IT systems, IT security, and data protection for
                                 financial institutions operating in Germany. These aim to ensure
                                 the security and stability of financial operations.</p>
                              <p><b>In Brief:</b> <a
                                    href="https://www.bafin.de/EN/Homepage/homepage_node.html"
                                    target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">BaFin</a> outlines
                                 specific IT security and data protection requirements for financial
                                 institutions operating in Germany to protect sensitive data and
                                 ensure system integrity.</p>
                           </li>
                        </ul>
                     </td>
                     <td style="width: 30%; vertical-align: top; padding: 15px;">
                        <!-- Placeholder: Update image path -->
                        <img width="2500" src="/static/app/Data_Compliance_Pipelines/emea.png" />
                     </td>
                  </tr>
               </table>
            </ul>
         </html>
      </panel>
   </row>
   <row id="tab_apjc">
      <panel>
         <html>
            <ul>
               <h1>
                  <!-- Placeholder: Update icon path -->
                  <img width="35"
                     src="/static/app/Data_Compliance_Pipelines/SA_image_icon_target.png" />
                  <b>APJC REGULATIONS</b>
               </h1>
               <table>
                  <tr>
                     <td>
                        <ul>
                           <li>
                              <p><b>MAS Notices &amp; Guidelines (Singapore):</b> The <a
                                    href="https://www.mas.gov.sg/" target="_blank"
                                    rel="noopener noreferrer">Monetary
                                    Authority of Singapore (MAS)</a> issues various notices,
                                 guidelines, and circulars that set out regulatory requirements for
                                 financial institutions in Singapore. These cover areas such as
                                 technology risk management (<a
                                    href="https://www.mas.gov.sg/regulation/guidelines/technology-risk-management-guidelines"
                                    target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">TRM</a>),
                                 cybersecurity, data governance, outsourcing, and business
                                 continuity management, aiming to ensure the safety and soundness of
                                 the financial sector.</p>
                              <p><b>In Brief:</b> <a href="https://www.mas.gov.sg/" target="_blank"
                                    rel="noopener noreferrer">MAS</a> regulations focus on robust
                                 technology risk management frameworks, cybersecurity measures, and
                                 data governance practices for financial institutions in Singapore.</p>
                           </li>
                           <li>
                              <p><b>RMiT (Risk Management in Technology) (Malaysia):</b> Issued by
                                 Bank Negara Malaysia (the central bank), the <a
                                    href="https://www.bnm.gov.my/documents/20124/938039/Risk+Management+in+Technology+(RMiT).pdf"
                                    target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Risk Management in
                                 Technology (RMiT)</a> policy outlines the requirements for
                                 financial institutions to establish a robust technology risk
                                 management framework and practices. This includes governance, IT
                                 infrastructure security, cybersecurity resilience, data management,
                                 and oversight of third-party service providers.</p>
                              <p><b>In Brief:</b> <a
                                    href="https://www.bnm.gov.my/documents/20124/938039/Risk+Management+in+Technology+(RMiT).pdf"
                                    target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">RMiT</a> is Bank
                                 Negara Malaysia's policy requiring financial institutions to
                                 establish comprehensive technology risk management, including data
                                 security and cyber resilience measures.</p>
                           </li>
                           <li>
                              <p><b>APPI (Act on Protection of Personal Information) (Japan):</b>
                                 Japan's <a href="https://www.ppc.go.jp/en/legal/" target="_blank"
                                    rel="noopener noreferrer">APPI</a> is the primary legislation
                                 governing the handling of personal information by businesses. It
                                 sets out rules for the collection, use, storage, and transfer of
                                 personal data, and grants individuals rights regarding their
                                 information. It has undergone amendments to align more closely with
                                 international standards like <a href="https://gdpr-info.eu/"
                                    target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">GDPR</a>.</p>
                              <p><b>In Brief:</b> <a href="https://www.ppc.go.jp/en/legal/"
                                    target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">APPI</a> is Japan's
                                 primary data privacy law regulating the handling of personal
                                 information by businesses, covering collection, use, security, and
                                 providing individuals with rights over their data.</p>
                           </li>
                           <li>
                              <p><b>Cross-Border Data Transfer Rules (Various Countries):</b> Many
                                 countries in the <a
                                    href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Asia-Pacific"
                                    target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">APJC</a> region have
                                 specific national laws or regulations that govern how personal and
                                 sensitive data can be transferred outside their borders. These
                                 rules vary significantly and may require consent, adequacy
                                 assessments of the recipient country's data protection laws, or the
                                 implementation of specific contractual safeguards to ensure data
                                 protection.</p>
                              <p><b>In Brief:</b> Numerous national laws across <a
                                    href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Asia-Pacific"
                                    target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">APJC</a> impose
                                 specific requirements for transferring personal and financial data
                                 outside of each respective country, often requiring specific
                                 consent or mechanisms.</p>
                           </li>
                        </ul>
                     </td>
                     <td style="width: 30%; vertical-align: top; padding: 15px;">
                        <!-- Placeholder: Update image path -->
                        <img width="2500" src="/static/app/Data_Compliance_Pipelines/apjc.png" />
                     </td>
                  </tr>
               </table>
            </ul>
         </html>
      </panel>
   </row>
   <row id="tab_anz">
      <panel>
         <html>
            <ul>
               <h1>
                  <!-- Placeholder: Update icon path -->
                  <img width="35"
                     src="/static/app/Data_Compliance_Pipelines/SA_image_icon_target.png" />
                  <b>A/NZ REGULATIONS</b>
               </h1>
               <table>
                  <tr>
                     <td>
                        <ul>
                           <li>
                              <b>CPS 234 (Information Security) (Australia)</b>
                              <p>Issued by the <a href="https://www.apra.gov.au/" target="_blank"
                                    rel="noopener noreferrer">Australian Prudential Regulation
                                 Authority (APRA)</a>, <a
                                    href="https://www.apra.gov.au/prudential-standard-cps-234-information-security"
                                    target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">CPS 234</a> is a
                                 prudential standard that requires <a
                                    href="https://www.apra.gov.au/" target="_blank"
                                    rel="noopener noreferrer">APRA</a>-regulated entities (such as
                                 banks, insurers, and superannuation funds) to implement and
                                 maintain information security controls to protect their information
                                 assets (including data) from internal and external threats.</p>
                              <p><b>In Brief:</b> <a
                                    href="https://www.apra.gov.au/prudential-standard-cps-234-information-security"
                                    target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">CPS 234</a> requires <a
                                    href="https://www.apra.gov.au/" target="_blank"
                                    rel="noopener noreferrer">APRA</a>-regulated entities to
                                 maintain information security capabilities commensurate with their
                                 risk profiles to protect information assets, including data.</p>
                           </li>
                           <li>
                              <b>CPS 230 (Operational Resilience) (Australia)</b>
                              <p><a href="https://www.apra.gov.au/" target="_blank"
                                    rel="noopener noreferrer">APRA</a>'s <a
                                    href="https://www.apra.gov.au/prudential-standard-cps-230-operational-risk-management"
                                    target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">CPS 230</a> is a
                                 prudential standard designed to strengthen the operational
                                 resilience of regulated entities. It sets requirements for managing
                                 operational risks, ensuring business continuity, and maintaining
                                 critical operations through disruptions, including those related to
                                 technology failures, cyber-attacks, and other incidents impacting
                                 data and systems.</p>
                              <p><b>In Brief:</b> <a
                                    href="https://www.apra.gov.au/prudential-standard-cps-230-operational-risk-management"
                                    target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">CPS 230</a> aims to
                                 strengthen operational resilience for <a
                                    href="https://www.apra.gov.au/" target="_blank"
                                    rel="noopener noreferrer">APRA</a>-regulated entities by
                                 establishing requirements for managing operational risks, including
                                 those impacting data and systems.</p>
                           </li>
                           <li>
                              <b>Privacy Act 1988 (Australia)</b>
                              <p>This is <a
                                    href="https://www.legislation.gov.au/Details/C2021C00400"
                                    target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Australia's Privacy
                                 Act 1988</a>. It includes the <a
                                    href="https://www.oaic.gov.au/privacy/australian-privacy-principles"
                                    target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Australian Privacy
                                 Principles (APPs)</a> that govern the collection, use, disclosure,
                                 storage, and security of personal information, and also includes a
                                 mandatory Notifiable Data Breaches (<a
                                    href="https://www.oaic.gov.au/privacy/notifiable-data-breaches"
                                    target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">NDB</a>) scheme.</p>
                              <p><b>In Brief:</b> <a
                                    href="https://www.legislation.gov.au/Details/C2021C00400"
                                    target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Australia's Privacy
                                 Act</a> governs how personal information is handled by businesses,
                                 setting out privacy principles for collection, use, storage, and
                                 disclosure, and includes mandatory data breach notification.</p>
                           </li>
                           <li>
                              <b>Privacy Act 2020 (New Zealand)</b>
                              <p><a href="https://www.privacy.org.nz/privacy-act-2020/"
                                    target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">New Zealand's Privacy
                                 Act 2020</a> modernizes the country's privacy laws. It includes <a
                                    href="https://www.privacy.org.nz/privacy-act-2020/information-privacy-principles/"
                                    target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Information Privacy
                                 Principles (IPPs)</a> that govern how agencies collect, use, store,
                                 and disclose personal information. Key features include mandatory
                                 data breach notifications and new rules for cross-border data
                                 transfers.</p>
                              <p><b>In Brief:</b> <a
                                    href="https://www.privacy.org.nz/privacy-act-2020/"
                                    target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">New Zealand's Privacy
                                 Act</a> outlines principles for the collection, use, storage, and
                                 disclosure of personal information, providing individuals with
                                 rights and establishing breach notification requirements.</p>
                           </li>
                           <li>
                              <b>Consumer Data Right (CDR) (Australia)</b>
                              <p>The <a href="https://www.cdr.gov.au/" target="_blank"
                                    rel="noopener noreferrer">CDR</a> legislation in Australia gives
                                 consumers greater access to and control over their data held by
                                 businesses. Initially rolled out in the banking sector (Open
                                 Banking), it is expanding to other sectors. It allows consumers to
                                 direct accredited data recipients to securely access their data to
                                 get better deals on products and services, imposing data security
                                 and privacy obligations on participating entities.</p>
                              <p><b>In Brief:</b> <a href="https://www.cdr.gov.au/" target="_blank"
                                    rel="noopener noreferrer">CDR</a> is legislation allowing
                                 Australian consumers to securely access and share their data held
                                 by accredited businesses, including those in the financial sector,
                                 impacting data portability and security requirements.</p>
                           </li>
                        </ul>
                     </td>
                     <td style="width: 30%; vertical-align: top; padding: 15px;">
                        <!-- Placeholder: Update image path -->
                        <img width="2500" src="/static/app/Data_Compliance_Pipelines/anz.png" />
                     </td>
                  </tr>
               </table>
            </ul>
         </html>
      </panel>
   </row>
   <row id="tab_next">
      <panel>
         <html tokens="true">
            <ul>
               <h1>
                  <!-- Placeholder: Update icon path -->
                  <img width="45"
                     src="/static/app/Data_Compliance_Pipelines/SA_image_icon_ques.png" />
                  <!-- Updated Help Header -->
                  <b>Do you need help? Ask a Data Compliance Expert.</b>
               </h1>
               <p> Need help with your environment or requirements? Send us your questions, and
                  we’ll get back to you as soon as possible. <ul>
                     <li> For detailed step-by-step instructions on implementing the solution using
                  this Solutions Accelerator, visit our <a
                           href="https://lantern.splunk.com/Industry_Use_Cases/Financial_Services_and_Insurance/Solution_Accelerator_for_Data_Compliance_Pipelines">
                           <b>Solutions Accelerator</b>
                        </a> page.</li>
                     <li> To expedite implementation with professional services, please reach out to
                  our sales team by clicking <a
                           href="https://www.splunk.com/en_us/ask-an-expert.html?expertCode=data_compliance_solutions_accelerator"
                           target="_ask_expert">
                           <b>Contact Us</b>
                        </a>
                     </li>
                     <li> If you need immediate assistance, explore our community forum, <a
                           href="http://answers.splunk.com/">
                           <b>Splunk Answers</b>
                        </a>.</li>
                  </ul>
               </p>
               <!-- Placeholder: Update bullet image path -->
               <img src="/static/app/Data_Compliance_Pipelines/SA_image_bullet_03.png" />
               <a
                  href="https://www.splunk.com/en_us/ask-an-expert.html?expertCode=data_compliance_solutions_accelerator"
                  class="btn" target="_ask_expert">Contact Us</a>
            </ul>

         </html>
      </panel>
   </row>
</dashboard>